behrouzbiryani.com 2019-04-13

# Behrouz Biryani - Privacy Policy

  * Your IP is logged when placing an order. This is for reasons of fraud protection. Fraudulent orders will be submitted to the appropriate authorities.
  * Behrouz collects personally identifiable information that you may voluntarily provide on online forms, which may include: user registration, contact requests, guest comments, online surveys, and other online activities. The personally identifiable information (Personal Information) collected on this Site / our Mobile Application can include some or all of the following: your name, address, telephone number, email addresses, demographic information, and any other information you may voluntarily provide.
  * In addition to the Personal Information identified above, our web servers automatically identify computers by their IP addresses. Company may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site track users movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. To emphasize, IP addresses are not linked to Personal.
  * We may disclose to third party services certain personally identifiable information. Information you provide us such as name, email, mobile phone number. Information we collect as you access and use our service, including device information, location and network carrier. This information is shared with third party service providers so that we can personalize the app for you, performing behavioral analytics.

  * It is your own responsibility to ensure that you are fully aware of all of these terms and conditions when making a purchase on www.behrouzbiryani.com or partner Mobile Applications.
  * Behrouz reserves the right to change / modify these terms & conditions at their own discretion anytime.
  * The images shown are only indicative in nature & the actual product may vary in size, colour etc.
  * Behrouz reserves the right to change any part or piece of information on this web site without any notice to customers or visitors.
